<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<title>
	<en>Kumbh 2019</en>
	<hn>कुंभ 2019</hn>
	<sp>Spanish</sp>
	<fr>Kumbh 2019</fr>
    <ge>Kumbh 2019</ge>
    <it>Kumbh 2019</it>
    <po>Kumbh 2019</po>
</title>


<text>
	<en>In Prayagraj, as the word Kumbh enters ones ears the picturesque vision of Triveni Sangam, the sacred confluence of the Ganga, the Yamuna and the mystical Saraswati flashes in the minds of people. At the sacred confluence huge multitudes move like waves in the ocean filled with sense of devotion. ‘Shahi Snaan’ of Akharas, chanting of vedic mantras and elucidations of religious hymns in the Saint pandals, proclamations of knowledge, tatvamimansa and truth by rishis, charming music, mesmerising sound of multitudes of instruments, holy dip in sangam with utmost devotion fills the heart of devotees with immense joy and offering prayers at many divine temples exhibits the greatness of Prayagraj Kumbh.</en>
	<hn>प्रयागराज में, कुंभ शब्द के रूप में कानों में प्रवेश करता है त्रिवेणी संगम की सुरम्य दृष्टि, गंगा का पवित्र संगम, यमुना और रहस्यमय सरस्वती लोगों के दिमाग में चमकती है। पवित्र संगम पर विशाल बहुसंख्यक भक्ति की भावना से भरे महासागर में तरंगों की तरह आगे बढ़ते हैं। अक्षरों के शाही सना ', संत मंडल में धार्मिक भजनों के धार्मिक मंत्रों और धार्मिक भजनों की व्याख्या, ज्ञान की घोषणा, तपस्यामंद और ऋषियों द्वारा सच्चाई, आकर्षक संगीत, उपकरणों की संख्या में मज़ेदार ध्वनि, अत्यंत भक्ति के साथ संगम में पवित्र डुबकी भरती है कई दिव्य मंदिरों में अत्यधिक आनंद और भेंट के साथ भक्तों का दिल प्रयागराज कुंभ की महानता प्रदर्शित करता है।</hn>
	<sp>En Prayagraj, cuando la palabra Kumbh entra en sus oídos, la visión pintoresca de Triveni Sangam, la confluencia sagrada del Ganga, el Yamuna y el místico Saraswati destella en las mentes de las personas. En la confluencia sagrada, grandes multitudes se mueven como olas en el océano llenas de sentido de devoción. 'Shahi Snaan' de Akharas, canto de mantras védicos y elucidaciones de himnos religiosos en los Santos de los pandales, proclamaciones de conocimiento, tatvamimansa y verdad por rishis, música encantadora, fascinante sonido de multitud de instrumentos, inmersión sagrada en sangam con absoluta devoción llena el El corazón de los devotos con inmensa alegría y oraciones en muchos templos divinos muestra la grandeza de Prayagraj Kumbh.</sp>
	<fr>À Prayagraj, lorsque le mot Kumbh entre dans nos oreilles, nous voyons la vision pittoresque de Triveni Sangam, la confluence sacrée du Ganga, du Yamuna et de la mystique Saraswati dans l’esprit des gens. À la confluence sacrée, d’énormes multitudes se meuvent comme des vagues dans l’océan emplies de sens de la dévotion. 'Shahi Snaan' d'Akharas, chants de mantras védiques et élucidations d'hymnes religieux dans les saints pandals, proclamations de la connaissance, tatvamimansa et vérité par des rishis, musique charmante, son hypnotique de multitudes d'instruments, dévotion sacrée à sangam remplie de dévotion Le cœur des fidèles avec une joie immense et des prières dans de nombreux temples divins témoigne de la grandeur de Prayagraj Kumbh.</fr>
	<ge>In Prayagraj, wenn das Wort Kumbh in die Ohren kommt, blitzt die malerische Vision von Triveni Sangam, der heilige Zusammenfluss der Ganga, der Yamuna und der mystischen Saraswati in den Köpfen der Menschen. Am heiligen Zusammenfluss bewegen sich riesige Mengen wie Wellen im Meer voller Hingabe. 'Shahi Snaan' von Akharas, Chanten von vedischen Mantras und Erklärungen von religiösen Hymnen in den heiligen Pandalen, Verkündigungen von Wissen, tatvamimansa und Wahrheit durch Rishis, bezaubernde Musik, hypnotisierender Klang von vielen Instrumenten, heiliger Einbruch in Sangam mit äußerster Hingabe füllt die Das Herz der Gläubigen mit großer Freude und Gebete in vielen göttlichen Tempeln zeigt die Größe von Prayagraj Kumbh.</ge>
	<it>In Prayagraj, come la parola Kumbh, entra nelle orecchie la visione pittoresca di Triveni Sangam, la sacra confluenza del Gange, la Yamuna e il mistico Saraswati lampeggia nelle menti delle persone. Alla sacra confluenza enormi moltitudini si muovono come onde nell'oceano piene di senso di devozione. 'Shahi Snaan' di Akharas, canto dei mantra vedici e delucidazioni di inni religiosi nei pandals Saint, proclami di conoscenza, tatvamimansa e verità di rishi, musica affascinante, suono ipnotico di una moltitudine di strumenti, santi tuffo nel sangam con la massima devozione riempie il cuore di devoti con immensa gioia e offerta di preghiere in molti templi divini mostra la grandezza di Prayagraj Kumbh.</it>
	<po>Em Prayagraj, quando a palavra Kumbh entra nos ouvidos, a visão pitoresca de Triveni Sangam, a sagrada confluência do Ganga, do Yamuna e do místico Saraswati, brilha nas mentes das pessoas. Na sagrada confluência, imensas multidões se movem como ondas no oceano, cheias de senso de devoção. 'Shahi Snaan' de Akharas, cantando de mantras védicos e elucidações de hinos religiosos nos pandals de Saint, proclamações de conhecimento, tatvamimansa e verdade por rishis, música encantadora, som hipnotizante de multidões de instrumentos, mergulho sagrado em sangam com devoção máxima enche o coração de devotos com imensa alegria e oferecendo orações em muitos templos divinos exibe a grandeza de Prayagraj Kumbh</po>
</text>
	</root>
